{
    "subject": "Richard_Francis_Burton",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Isabel_Burton",
    "human_readable": "Richard Francis Burton is married to Isabel Burton.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885876178741455,
            "question": "Is Isabel Burton married to Richard Francis Burton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9647915959358215,
            "question": "Who is Richard Francis Burton married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9296057820320129,
            "question": "What is the name of the person Richard Francis Burton was married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9190297722816467,
            "question": "Who is the spouse of Richard Francis Burton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8812729120254517,
            "question": "Who was Richard Francis Burton's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8647518754005432,
            "question": "To whom did Richard Francis Burton have a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8347192406654358,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of Richard Francis Burton's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8227666616439819,
            "question": "What is the name of Richard Francis Burton's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7963879108428955,
            "question": "What was the name of Richard Francis Burton's partner in marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6773260235786438,
            "question": "With whom did Richard Francis Burton share a marital bond?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Richard Francis Burton is married to Isabel Burton.",
            "html": "yago_1312_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Richard Francis Burton's partner in marriage?",
            "html": "yago_1312_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Richard Francis Burton's wife?",
            "html": "yago_1312_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the name of Richard Francis Burton's wife?",
            "html": "yago_1312_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1312_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to test any more triples! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Richard Francis Burton is married to Isabel Burton. This can be seen from multiple references in the texts, including details about their relationship and Isabel's biography of Sir Richard Burton."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}